[Speed and Love]
[السرعة والحب]
[Episode 9]
[الحلقة 9]
No.
لا.
After all, he's still my father.
فهو في النهاية لا يزال والدي.
-Can't you just... -Apple.
- ألا يمكنك فقط... - أبل.
I don't like mealy apples.
لا أحب التفاح ذو القوام الدقيقي.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Call me when you've made up your mind.
اتصل بي عندما تتخذ قرارك.
You're quite confident, huh?
أنت واثق جداً، أليس كذلك؟
What makes you think
ما الذي يجعلك تفكر؟
I'd eat anything you feed me?
سآكل أي شيء تقدمه لي؟
Do you want her to keep bothering you?
هل تريدها أن تستمر في إزعاجك؟
I'm not afraid of that.
أنا لست خائفاً من ذلك.
Really?
حقًا؟
Not even afraid of a woman clinging to you?
ألا تخاف حتى من امرأة تتشبث بك؟
What's there to be afraid of?
ما الذي يدعو للخوف؟
It depends on which woman we're talking about.
الأمر يعتمد على أي امرأة نتحدث عنها.
Wan Qing?
وان تشينغ؟
She's nothing to be afraid of.
لا داعي للخوف منها.
What about other women?
وماذا عن النساء الأخريات؟
Who?
من؟
Who are you afraid of?
مِمَّن تخاف؟
In my entire life,
طوال حياتي،
I've never been afraid of anyone.
لم أشعر بالخوف من أحد قط.
You sure about that?
هل أنت متأكد من ذلك؟
Maybe one day you'll meet a woman
ربما ستلتقي بامرأة في يوم من الأيام
you're really, really afraid of.
أنت خائف منه حقاً.
If that day comes,
إذا جاء ذلك اليوم،
I'll accept my fate.
سأتقبل قدري.
I specially found you
لقد وجدتك خصيصاً
a coach who speaks Chinese.
مدرب يتحدث الصينية.
This one.
هذا.
Coach Hua.
المدرب هوا.
Hello, Coach.
مرحباً يا مدرب.
I've been a top coach for ten years.
لقد كنت مدرباً متميزاً لمدة عشر سنوات.
You can trust me.
يمكنك الوثوق بي.
Congratulations, my lucky star,
ألف مبروك يا نجمي المحظوظ!
for passing your driving test!
تهانينا على اجتياز اختبار القيادة!
It's all thanks to you.
كل الفضل يعود إليك.
It's because you're naturally gifted.
ذلك لأنك موهوب بالفطرة.
Actually, I don't even know why,
في الحقيقة، لا أعرف حتى السبب.
but the moment I first saw you,
لكن في اللحظة التي رأيتك فيها لأول مرة،
I just wanted to be close to you.
أردت فقط أن أكون قريباً منك.
That's no mystery.
هذا ليس لغزاً.
It's because you're beautiful and kind.
ذلك لأنكِ جميلة ولطيفة.
Stop teasing. I'm being serious.
توقف عن المزاح. أنا جاد.
It might be a connection from our past lives.
قد يكون ذلك رابطاً من حياتنا الماضية.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
It's called...
يُطلق عليه اسم...
"instant..."
"فوري..."
"Instant connection!"
"اتصال فوري!"
Your Chinese is really good.
لغتك الصينية جيدة جداً.
You even know idioms.
بل إنك تعرف التعابير الاصطلاحية.
Xin,
اطلب،
why did your grades drop so fast?
لماذا انخفضت درجاتك بهذه السرعة؟
Did you not understand the lessons?
ألم تفهم الدروس؟
Xin,
اطلب،
you must study hard.
يجب عليك الدراسة بجد.
If I had studied hard back then,
لو كنت قد اجتهدت في دراستي آنذاك،
I wouldn't be a hoodlum now.
لن أصبح مجرماً الآن.
Are you cut out for studying?
هل أنت مؤهل للدراسة؟
Back then, a C was already
في ذلك الوقت، كان حرف C يُعتبر بالفعل
-way beyond your usual performance. -Go away.
- يتجاوز أداؤك المعتاد بكثير. - ارحل.
I've gotten a C before.
لقد حصلت على تقدير "جيد" من قبل.
You must
يجب عليك أن
take my words to heart.
خذوا كلامي على محمل الجد.
Okay, okay. I got it.
حسناً، حسناً. فهمت.
You really did?
هل فعلت ذلك حقاً؟
Then I'll sign this for you this time.
سأوقع لك هذه المرة.
Wait, Xin.
انتظر يا شين.
Do you understand all the questions you got wrong now?
هل تفهم الآن جميع الأسئلة التي أخطأت فيها؟
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
making mistakes isn't scary.
ارتكاب الأخطاء ليس أمراً مخيفاً.
What's scary is...
الأمر المخيف هو...
I think you're the scary.
أعتقد أنك أنت المخيف.
Are you signing it or not? If not, I will.
هل ستوقعها أم لا؟ إن لم تفعل، فسأوقعها أنا.
Why so many words?
لماذا كل هذه الكلمات؟
Xin,
اطلب،
how do you write Jin in Jin Zhao?
كيف تكتب اسم جين في جين تشاو؟
-Give me a break. -With your education level...
- ارحمني قليلاً. - بمستوى تعليمك...
Give it to me. I'll sign it.
أعطني إياه. سأوقعه.
I just can't recall right now.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر الآن.
Let me think.
دعني أفكر.
So rusty. Give it to me.
صدئ جداً. أعطني إياه.
Do you even know how to sign it? Give it to me.
هل تعرف حتى كيف توقعها؟ أعطني إياها.
-Who's going to sign it? -Me.
- من سيوقعها؟ - أنا.
I will. Give it to me.
سأفعل. أعطني إياه.
-Let me. -You know how to write it?
- دعني أفعل. - هل تعرف كيف تكتبها؟
You don't know how to write it. How can you sign it?
أنت لا تعرف كيف تكتبها. كيف يمكنك توقيعها؟
I'll sign it now. I remember it now.
سأوقعها الآن. أتذكرها الآن.
-Give it to me. -I'll sign it.
أعطني إياه. سأوقعه.
Brandy.
براندي.
Well...
حسنًا...
Brandy, don't get angry.
براندي، لا تغضبي.
One test doesn't mean anything.
اختبار واحد لا يعني شيئاً.
Right. Xin's actually been working hard.
صحيح. لقد كان شين يعمل بجد بالفعل.
Yes, she got an A before.
نعم، لقد حصلت على تقدير ممتاز من قبل.
She even got an A+ once. I signed those.
بل إنها حصلت على علامة امتياز (A+) مرة واحدة. لقد وقّعتُ على تلك الدرجات.
You... shut up!
أنت... اصمت!
These last two questions aren't hard.
هذان السؤالان الأخيران ليسا صعبين.
Why did you leave them blank?
لماذا تركتها فارغة؟
I did it on purpose.
فعلت ذلك عن قصد.
Why?
لماذا؟
The teacher said the first-place student
قال المعلم إن الطالب الحائز على المركز الأول
needs to give a speech as the student representative.
عليه أن يلقي خطاباً بصفته ممثلاً للطلاب.
I don't want to go.
لا أريد الذهاب.
You're getting more and more strong-willed as you grow up.
تزداد إرادتك قوةً مع تقدمك في العمر.
Not bad. I've only ever written reflections,
ليس سيئاً. لم أكتب سوى تأملات شخصية.
never given a speech.
لم يسبق له أن ألقى خطاباً.
I was afraid my mom would nag.
كنت أخشى أن تُلحّ أمي عليّ.
I didn't expect you guys to be even worse.
لم أتوقع أن تكونوا أسوأ من ذلك.
She's talking about you.
إنها تتحدث عنك.
I'll sign it for you this time.
سأوقعها لك هذه المرة.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
just talk to your teacher.
تحدث إلى معلمك.
Don't pull these little tricks.
لا تستخدم هذه الحيل الصغيرة.
I see.
أرى.
Yang, take her home.
يانغ، خذها إلى المنزل.
Yes, Master.
نعم يا سيدي.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
Be careful on your way.
كن حذراً في طريقك.
Aren't you a bit too strict with Xin?
ألا تعتبرين نفسكِ صارمة بعض الشيء مع شين؟
Too harsh. She's just a kid.
قاسية جداً. إنها مجرد طفلة.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
You two have pretended to be her parents
لقد تظاهرتما بأنكما والداها
signing her papers many times, haven't you?
لقد وقّعت على أوراقها مرات عديدة، أليس كذلك؟
I'm... I'm thirsty?
أنا... أنا عطشان؟
You want to buy a dog?
هل ترغب في شراء كلب؟
I sell cats too.
أبيع القطط أيضاً.
-I'm right next to the shop. -The connection is bad.
- أنا بجوار المتجر مباشرةً. - الاتصال سيء.
[Speeding Auto House]
[بيت سيارات السرعة]
I'll move somewhere else to talk.
سأنتقل إلى مكان آخر للتحدث.
Alright, alright.
حسناً، حسناً.
-I'll go somewhere else. -Okay, okay.
- سأذهب إلى مكان آخر. - حسناً، حسناً.
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
I...
أنا...
I'm thirsty.
أنا عطشان.
Hello, one milk tea please.
مرحباً، أريد كوباً واحداً من شاي الحليب من فضلك.
Here's your milk tea. Welcome back.
تفضل، شاي الحليب الخاص بك. أهلاً بعودتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
This looks cool.
هذا يبدو رائعاً.
The skills are a bit rough compared to mine.
مهاراتهم متواضعة بعض الشيء مقارنة بمهاراتي.
You're bragging.
أنت تتباهى.
Has the locking collar been adjusted?
هل تم ضبط طوق القفل؟
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Is it that obvious?
هل الأمر بهذه البساطة؟
There was a noise when you drove in.
كان هناك ضجيج عندما دخلت بالسيارة.
It's loose.
إنه مرتخي.
I just modified this car.
لقد قمتُ بتعديل هذه السيارة للتو.
Can you check it again for me?
هل يمكنك التحقق منه مرة أخرى من أجلي؟
See that?
أترى ذلك؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Right? And look here.
صحيح؟ وانظر هنا.
This engine doesn't suit this car.
هذا المحرك لا يناسب هذه السيارة.
And look,
وانظر،
the right locking collar is also broken.
كما أن طوق القفل الأيمن مكسور.
It needs to be fixed too, okay?
يجب إصلاحه أيضاً، حسناً؟
Okay.
تمام.
Lin Sui?
لين سوي؟
Why is he here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
[locking collar]
[طوق القفل]
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm meeting a friend here.
سأقابل صديقاً هنا.
You picked the worst-tasting one.
لقد اخترت أسوأها مذاقاً.
This one?
هذا؟
Which flavor tastes better then?
أي نكهة طعمها أفضل إذن؟
Come with me.
تعال معي.
I don't drink alcohol.
أنا لا أشرب الكحول.
Don't accuse me wrongly.
لا تتهمني زوراً.
This doesn't have any alcohol.
هذا المنتج لا يحتوي على أي كحول.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
No peach either.
ولا خوخ أيضاً.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
It's strawberry flavor?
هل هو بنكهة الفراولة؟
Welcome to my world.
أهلاً بكم في عالمي.
Hey, Lin Sui.
مرحباً، لين سوي.
We should go now.
يجب أن نذهب الآن.
Going up the mountain? I can give you a ride.
هل أنت ذاهب إلى أعلى الجبل؟ يمكنني أن أوصلك.
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
I arranged to meet Sanlai at the service area.
رتبت للقاء سانلاي في منطقة الخدمات.
Sanlai?
سانلاي؟
He's the one I invited.
هو الشخص الذي دعوته.
You could wait for him up the mountain.
يمكنك انتظاره أعلى الجبل.
You invited him? So you know each other?
هل دعوته؟ إذن أنتما تعرفان بعضكما؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
Just curious.
مجرد فضول.
Curious?
فضولي؟
Are you coming or not?
هل ستأتي أم لا؟
I'm lost. Wait for me on the mountain.
أنا تائه. انتظرني على الجبل.
Which car?
أي سيارة؟
That one.
هذا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
It's an understanding between drivers,
إنه تفاهم بين السائقين،
like a secret code.
مثل شفرة سرية.
Aren't you going to note it in your phone?
ألن تدون ذلك في هاتفك؟
It's not necessary.
ليس ذلك ضرورياً.
Hold on tight.
تمسك جيداً.
Don't touch it yet.
لا تلمسه بعد.
The engine's really hot right now.
المحرك ساخن جداً الآن.
Why hasn't he come yet?
لماذا لم يأتِ بعد؟
Lin Sui, look.
لين سوي، انظر.
That cute little pickup is heading up the mountain.
تلك الشاحنة الصغيرة اللطيفة تتجه نحو الجبل.
Do you think that guy is faking it?
هل تعتقد أن ذلك الرجل يتظاهر؟
If not,
وإلا،
it's even funnier.
بل إن الأمر أكثر طرافة.
Why did you call Sanlai here?
لماذا اتصلت بسانلاي هنا؟
That's something
هذا شيء
I'm wondering too.
وأنا أتساءل أيضاً.
Sanlai, what took you so long?
سانلاي، ما الذي أخّرك كل هذا الوقت؟
I've been waiting for you for an hour.
لقد كنت أنتظرك لمدة ساعة.
What's the rush?
ما الداعي للعجلة؟
It's such a big event.
إنه حدث ضخم للغاية.
I had to get myself properly dressed up.
كان عليّ أن أرتدي ملابس مناسبة.
The outfit looks good.
الزي يبدو جيداً.
But that red scarf...
لكن ذلك الوشاح الأحمر...
You have great taste.
ذوقك رائع.
This is for good luck—
هذا لجلب الحظ السعيد.
it means a victorious start.
وهذا يعني بداية موفقة.
Do you know
هل تعلم
when you were driving earlier,
عندما كنت تقود السيارة سابقاً،
that camera...
تلك الكاميرا...
Well...
حسنًا...
Let's get started.
لنبدأ.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
Brandy said
قالت براندي
this car is modified.
هذه السيارة معدلة.
1000 HP, 2000 torque,
1000 حصان، 2000 عزم دوران،
Wankel engine. It's faster than race cars on the track.
محرك وانكل. إنه أسرع من سيارات السباق على الحلبة.
Sorry.
آسف.
I didn't mean to take advantage of you.
لم أقصد استغلالك.
I should be a good host.
ينبغي أن أكون مضيفاً جيداً.
I'll give you a 5-second head start.
سأمنحك مهلة خمس ثوانٍ.
How's that?
كيف ذلك؟
Then I'll respectfully accept your offer.
سأقبل عرضك بكل احترام.
The guest follows the host.
يتبع الضيف المضيف.
Sanlai,
سانلاي،
are you okay? Be careful.
هل أنت بخير؟ كن حذراً.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I just used a little trick
لقد استخدمت خدعة صغيرة
and gained the upper hand.
وحقق التفوق.
Go back.
عُد.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Let's move!
هيا بنا نتحرك!
Looks like...
يبدو أن...
it won't take 5 seconds.
لن يستغرق الأمر 5 ثوانٍ.
I realized
أدركت ذلك
we need to follow the rules in games.
علينا اتباع القواعد في الألعاب.
You don't need to let me go first this time.
لستَ مضطراً لأن تدعني أذهب أولاً هذه المرة.
Let's go together.
هيا بنا نذهب معاً.
Give me the hat.
أعطني القبعة.
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
This hat isn't mine.
هذه القبعة ليست لي.
I need to return it to its owner.
أحتاج إلى إعادته إلى مالكه.
I'll return it for you.
سأعيدها لك.
There's a good cupcake shop
يوجد متجر جيد للكعك
at the service area down the mountain.
في منطقة الخدمات أسفل الجبل.
See you there.
أراك هناك.
If you get there within half an hour, it's on me.
إذا وصلت إلى هناك في غضون نصف ساعة، فسيكون الأمر على حسابي.
Today really got off to a bad start.
لقد بدأ اليوم بداية سيئة للغاية.
All this dressing up was for nothing.
كل هذا التأنق كان بلا جدوى.
You're a typical underachiever with lots of stationery.
أنت شخص نموذجي غير متفوق ولديه الكثير من الأدوات المكتبية.
Alright, let's head back.
حسنًا، لنعد أدراجنا.
Going up the mountain was so difficult.
كان صعود الجبل صعباً للغاية.
Going down must be much easier.
النزول سيكون أسهل بكثير.
You're wrong.
أنت مخطئ.
The downhill road is the hardest to drive.
الطريق المنحدر هو الأصعب للقيادة.
Why do I feel a little dizzy?
لماذا أشعر بدوار طفيف؟
I'll drive.
سأقود السيارة.
Jiang Mu,
جيانغ مو,
are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
It took me over an hour to drive up.
استغرقت الرحلة بالسيارة أكثر من ساعة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
We'll definitely get there within half an hour.
سنصل بالتأكيد في غضون نصف ساعة.
She only took 23 minutes.
استغرقت 23 دقيقة فقط.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
Two of each: black tea, green tea,
اثنان من كل نوع: شاي أسود، شاي أخضر،
and lemon flavors.
ونكهة الليمون.
And two without cream.
واثنان بدون كريمة.
Sanlai, why are you only buying the cake bases?
سانلاي، لماذا تشترين قواعد الكيك فقط؟
They're for Brandy.
إنها لبراندي.
Brandy never eats
براندي لا تأكل أبداً
the cream on cake.
الكريمة على الكعكة.
I don't even know
لا أعرف حتى
what's left of a cupcake without cream.
ما تبقى من كعكة صغيرة بدون كريمة.
He's not really into sweets.
هو ليس مولعاً بالحلويات.
You know he doesn't like sweets?
هل تعلم أنه لا يحب الحلويات؟
That habit of his
تلك العادة لديه
is a bit annoying, isn't it?
إنه أمر مزعج بعض الشيء، أليس كذلك؟
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
why did Lin Sui take your hat earlier?
لماذا أخذ لين سوي قبعتك في وقت سابق؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
That guy is pretty weird.
ذلك الرجل غريب الأطوار نوعاً ما.
I already told him
لقد أخبرته بالفعل
that the hat wasn't mine
أن القبعة لم تكن لي
and that I needed to return it to its owner.
وأنه كان عليّ إعادته إلى مالكه.
But Lin said,
لكن لين قال:
"I'll return it to him for you."
"سأعيدها إليه نيابةً عنك."
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
Does he even know whose hat it is?
هل يعرف حتى لمن هذه القبعة؟
Whose is it?
لمن هذا؟
It's Brandy's.
إنه براندي.
Sir, your cakes are ready.
سيدي، كعكاتك جاهزة.
Thanks. How much is it in total?
شكراً. كم السعر الإجمالي؟
Someone already paid for you.
لقد دفع أحدهم ثمنك بالفعل.
Already paid?
هل تم الدفع مسبقاً؟
Yes.
نعم.
Who was it?
من كان؟
Sanlai,
سانلاي،
do you know how long it took us
هل تعلم كم استغرقنا من الوقت؟
to get down the mountain just now?
كيف يمكنني النزول من الجبل الآن؟
Not sure.
لست متأكداً.
40 or 50 minutes?
40 أو 50 دقيقة؟
23 minutes.
23 دقيقة.
23 minutes?
23 دقيقة؟
Turn on the lights if you want to take photos with the car.
قم بتشغيل الأضواء إذا كنت ترغب في التقاط صور مع السيارة.
Hey handsome, you're cute!
يا وسيم، أنت لطيف!
Can we take a photo with you?
هل يمكننا التقاط صورة معك؟
Come on, come on, together.
هيا بنا، هيا بنا، معاً.
Make me look cool.
اجعلني أبدو رائعاً.
Three, two, one.
ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد.
One more, one more!
واحد آخر، واحد آخر!
Come on.
تعال.
Thank you, handsome.
شكراً لك أيها الوسيم.
Thanks!
شكرًا!
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Your car looks great too.
سيارتك تبدو رائعة أيضاً.
-Thank you. You have good taste! -Bye-bye.
شكراً لك. ذوقك رفيع! مع السلامة.
Don't forget me next time you want to take a photo.
لا تنساني في المرة القادمة التي تريد فيها التقاط صورة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Bye-bye!
وداعا وداعا!
Sanlai,
سانلاي،
looks like you're quite popular.
يبدو أنك تحظى بشعبية كبيرة.
So why do you make yourself
فلماذا تجعل نفسك
look like this?
هل تبدو هكذا؟
Why don't you spruce yourself up a bit?
لماذا لا تهتم بمظهرك قليلاً؟
Look like what?
كيف تبدو؟
I put a lot of effort into this look.
لقد بذلت جهداً كبيراً في هذه الإطلالة.
Yes, I can see that.
نعم، أستطيع أن أرى ذلك.
It's just that your hair
الأمر فقط أن شعرك
is kind of covering your eyes.
إنه نوع من تغطية العينين.
Well,
حسنًا،
it's mainly because I'm just too charming.
السبب الرئيسي هو أنني ببساطة ساحر للغاية.
I'm afraid the girls will be so distracted when they see me
أخشى أن تتشتت انتباه الفتيات كثيراً عندما يرينني
that they won't be able to move,
أنهم لن يتمكنوا من التحرك،
and it'll affect my pet shop business.
وسيؤثر ذلك على أعمال متجر الحيوانات الأليفة الخاص بي.
That's why
لهذا السبب
I make my handsomeness
أصنع وسامتي
look a bit mysterious.
تبدو غامضة بعض الشيء.
You really put a lot of thought into that.
لقد فكرت في ذلك كثيراً.
Of course.
بالطبع.
I mean it.
أعني ذلك.
If you trim your beard
إذا قمت بتقليم لحيتك
and cut your hair a bit shorter,
وقص شعرك أقصر قليلاً،
you may look much fresher.
قد تبدو أكثر نضارة.
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
Yes.
نعم.
I think maybe you'll even become
أعتقد أنك ربما ستصبح حتى
more popular than Brandy.
أكثر شعبية من براندي.
Girl,
بنت،
since you said that,
بما أنك قلت ذلك،
I'll have to
سأضطر إلى
get rid of this haircut
تخلص من هذه القصة
and my beard.
ولحيتي.
Come on, I'll take you home.
هيا، سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
Home?
بيت؟
[Speeding Auto House]
[بيت سيارات السرعة]
What's gotten into you?
ما الذي أصابك؟
Jiang Mu told me
قال لي جيانغ مو
I'd look fresher this way.
سأبدو أكثر نضارة بهذه الطريقة.
So, what do you think?
إذن، ما رأيك؟
Still as handsome as ever, right?
لا يزال وسيماً كما كان دائماً، أليس كذلك؟
But I think
لكنني أعتقد
I'm a bit more handsome than you now.
أنا الآن أكثر وسامة منك بقليل.
Here.
هنا.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
-Mu, you're here. -Mu.
-مو، أنت هنا. -مو.
Sanlai?
سانلاي؟
You... you...
أنت... أنت...
Why do you look like this now?
لماذا تبدو هكذا الآن؟
Like what?
مثل ماذا؟
You had a haircut and you shaved?
هل قصصت شعرك وحلقت ذقنك؟
I didn't know your features were so sharp.
لم أكن أعلم أن ملامحك بهذه الحدة.
It's the first time I've seen your forehead.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أرى فيها جبهتك.
This style is so trendy,
هذا النمط عصري للغاية،
like an idol.
مثل الصنم.
How do you like it? I just bought all of this.
كيف وجدتها؟ لقد اشتريت كل هذا للتو.
You look much cooler this way.
تبدو أكثر أناقة بهذه الطريقة.
These beads are so cute.
هذه الخرزات لطيفة للغاية.
Do they come in colors?
هل تأتي بألوان مختلفة؟
I want the same ones.
أريد نفس النوع.
I got them for 19.90 at the store next door.
اشتريتها مقابل 19.90 من المتجر المجاور.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
Look.
ينظر.
Not bad, really.
ليس سيئاً حقاً.
Jiang Mu.
جيانغ مو.
Look at this. Do you like it?
انظر إلى هذا. هل يعجبك؟
Jiang Mu!
جيانغ مو!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
I'll go first.
سأبدأ أولاً.
Did you see Sanlai?
هل رأيت سانلاي؟
He's completely changed.
لقد تغير تماماً.
-Completely... -I hear you always ask Sanlai about me.
-بالتأكيد... -سمعت أنك تسأل سانلاي عني دائماً.
What did you find out?
ماذا اكتشفت؟
Not much.
ليس كثيراً.
You know him. He always
أنت تعرفه. إنه دائماً
goes off on tangents
ينحرف عن الموضوع ويتطرق إلى مواضيع جانبية
and can't stop praising himself.
ولا يتوقف عن مدح نفسه.
But I have to say, with this new look,
لكن عليّ أن أقول، مع هذا المظهر الجديد،
he's actually quite handsome.
إنه في الواقع وسيم للغاية.
Look at how he's...
انظر كيف هو...
You're not mad
أنت لست غاضباً
because I always pry into your business,
لأنني دائماً ما أتدخل في شؤونك الخاصة،
are you?
أنت؟
Why do you want to know about my business?
لماذا تريد معرفة المزيد عن عملي؟
Because it's you.
لأنه أنت.
You know very well
أنت تعلم جيداً
that we're not blood‑related.
أننا لسنا أقارب بالدم.
We lived together for a while when we were young,
عشنا معاً لفترة من الوقت عندما كنا صغاراً،
but back then you were just a child.
لكنك كنت حينها مجرد طفل.
Now,
الآن،
you keep coming here.
تستمر في المجيء إلى هنا.
What will others think if they find out?
ماذا سيظن الآخرون إذا علموا بذلك؟
What will Jin Qiang think?
ماذا سيفكر جين تشيانغ؟
Or do you just...
أم أنك فقط...
want something to happen...
أريد أن يحدث شيء ما...
between us?
بيننا؟
Mu!
في!
I'll bring... I...
سأحضر... أنا...
What's going on here?
ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
[Jin's Chinese Restaurant]
[مطعم جين الصيني]
Three cases of beer.
ثلاث علب من البيرة.
Three cases of beer. That's correct.
ثلاث علب من البيرة. هذا صحيح.
Why doesn't it add up?
لماذا لا يبدو الأمر منطقياً؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
It's you again.
أنت مرة أخرى.
We have customers. Go sleep somewhere else.
لدينا زبائن. اذهب للنوم في مكان آخر.
Go sleep somewhere else! Hurry up!
اذهب للنوم في مكان آخر! أسرع!
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
We've sold out of all our dishes today.
نفدت جميع أطباقنا اليوم.
Only dumplings are left.
لم يتبق سوى الزلابية.
Meat or vegetable dumplings?
زلابية باللحم أم بالخضار؟
Which one would you like?
أي واحد تفضل؟
You recommend one.
أنت توصي بواحد.
Okay then. Please take a seat.
حسناً، تفضل بالجلوس.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Here are your dumplings.
تفضلوا، هذه هي الزلابية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
The condiments are here.
التوابل موجودة هنا.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
Zhao.
تشاو.
Zhao, help me watch the shop.
تشاو، ساعدني في مراقبة المتجر.
There's a customer inside.
يوجد زبون بالداخل.
Give him whatever he asks for.
أعطه كل ما يطلبه.
-Okay. -I'll go get something next door.
-حسنًا. -سأذهب لأحضر شيئًا من المتجر المجاور.
Yours looks more delicious.
يبدو طبقك ألذ.
My dumplings are too salty.
الزلابية التي أتناولها مالحة جداً.
Your fried rice looks...
يبدو الأرز المقلي الذي أعددته...
pretty good.
جيد جداً.
Finish your food and leave.
أنهِ طعامك وانصرف.
Don't come back again.
لا تعود مرة أخرى.
I'm here to return something.
أنا هنا لأعيد شيئاً ما.
Let's have a talk.
لنتحدث.
Was that you on the mountain that night?
هل كنت أنت على الجبل تلك الليلة؟
I never expected the person I've been looking for all this time
لم أتوقع أبداً أن يكون الشخص الذي كنت أبحث عنه طوال هذا الوقت
to be you.
أن تكون أنت.
Don't you remember?
ألا تتذكر؟
Last time you barged into my racing team
في المرة الماضية اقتحمت فريق السباق الخاص بي
when I wasn't paying attention.
عندما لم أكن منتبهاً.
And the boxing match.
ومباراة الملاكمة.
I want you to fight a match for me.
أريدك أن تخوض مباراة من أجلي.
Your opponent is He Zhang from Wan Shengbang's team.
خصمك هو هي تشانغ من فريق وان شنغ بانغ.
If you win,
إذا فزت،
I'll give you a sum of money.
سأعطيك مبلغاً من المال.
I'll let you know the time and place later.
سأخبرك بالوقت والمكان لاحقاً.
I didn't expect you
لم أكن أتوقعك
to run away halfway through the fight.
أن يهرب في منتصف المعركة.
Then a pink pickup showed up,
ثم ظهرت شاحنة صغيرة وردية اللون.
and the owner actually admitted
واعترف المالك بذلك بالفعل
that he was the one driving that night.
أنه هو من كان يقود السيارة في تلك الليلة.
I agreed to race him, though I was suspicious.
وافقت على أن أتسابق معه، رغم أنني كنت متشككاً.
That guy
ذلك الرجل
was arranged by you, right?
أنت من رتبت الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
One race,
سباق واحد،
just the two of us.
نحن الاثنان فقط.
There's no need.
لا داعي لذلك.
Liang Yanfeng drives faster than me.
يقود Liang Yanfeng أسرع مني.
Why don't you go find him instead?
لماذا لا تذهب أنت للبحث عنه بدلاً من ذلك؟
I've known him for many years.
أعرفه منذ سنوات عديدة.
He's never beaten me.
لم يسبق له أن هزمني.
But you have.
لكنك فعلت.
That's because I know the roads better.
ذلك لأني أعرف الطرق بشكل أفضل.
Just happened to be lucky.
لقد حالفني الحظ فحسب.
One more time.
مرة أخرى.
Not interested.
غير مهتم.
So what
وماذا في ذلك
would make you interested?
هل سيثير ذلك اهتمامك؟
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
I got information
حصلت على معلومات
that next up is the cornering speed race.
والخطوة التالية هي سباق السرعة عند المنعطفات.
Get prepared.
استعد.
Only one race left,
لم يتبق سوى سباق واحد،
and you can make the top 3.
ويمكنك أن تكون من بين أفضل 3.
I'm not confident.
لستُ واثقاً.
Last time,
آخر مرة،
I almost lost.
كادت أن أخسر.
There's still some time.
لا يزال هناك بعض الوقت.
Only by getting first
فقط من خلال الحصول على المركز الأول
can you transport their cargo.
هل يمكنك نقل بضائعهم؟
That way, Wan Shengbang's secret business will be cut off,
وبهذه الطريقة، سيتم قطع أعمال وان شنغ بانغ السرية.
and we'll get the evidence.
وسنحصل على الأدلة.
What's wrong? Having problems?
ما المشكلة؟ هل تواجه مشاكل؟
How did you
كيف فعلت ذلك؟
drive back then?
هل كنت تقود السيارة للخلف حينها؟
As a top racer,
بصفته متسابقًا من الطراز الرفيع،
one obviously needs
يحتاج المرء بوضوح
calmness,
الهدوء،
attentiveness,
الانتباه،
courage,
شجاعة،
and skill.
والمهارة.
All of this...
كل هذا...
is bullshit.
هذا هراء.
So what's really the most important?
إذن ما هو الأهم حقاً؟
Mastery.
الإتقان.
You need to master everything
عليك إتقان كل شيء
you're supposed to control.
من المفترض أن تتحكم.
What is a car?
ما هي السيارة؟
A car is an extension of your body.
السيارة امتداد لجسمك.
And you
وأنت
should become part of the car,
ينبغي أن يصبح جزءًا من السيارة،
the most essential part.
الجزء الأكثر أهمية.
You need to understand its breathing,
عليك أن تفهم طريقة تنفسه،
its rhythm,
إيقاعه،
its sound,
صوته،
and its temperature.
ودرجة حرارته.
Of course,
بالطبع،
with just these things,
بهذه الأشياء فقط،
it's not enough
هذا لا يكفي
for one to become a top racer.
لكي يصبح المرء متسابقًا من الطراز الأول.
You need to be so skilled
يجب أن تكون ماهراً للغاية
that your hands are faster than your brain,
أن يديك أسرع من عقلك،
making all your movements
القيام بكل تحركاتك
become muscle memory
تصبح ذاكرة عضلية
and every decision and action
وكل قرار وفعل
happens instinctively,
يحدث بشكل غريزي،
without thinking.
دون تفكير.
Want to know how to achieve this?
هل تريد معرفة كيفية تحقيق ذلك؟
Come help me deliver food tomorrow.
تعال وساعدني في توصيل الطعام غداً.
Let your body
دع جسدك
drive your car.
قم بقيادة سيارتك.
Is there a simpler way to put it?
هل هناك طريقة أبسط لشرح ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Don't be a coward.
لا تكن جباناً.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Drive carefully.
قد بحذر.
Drink moderately.
اشرب باعتدال.
I'll come see you tomorrow.
سأزورك غداً.
You brat.
يا لك من طفل مزعج.
Or do you just...
أم أنك فقط...
want something to happen...
أريد أن يحدث شيء ما...
between us?
بيننا؟
So annoying.
مزعج للغاية.
[Speeding Auto House]
[بيت سيارات السرعة]
Jiang Mu,
جيانغ مو,
I made seafood hotpot today.
لقد أعددت اليوم طبق حساء المأكولات البحرية.
Come over tonight and eat with us.
تعالوا الليلة وتناولوا الطعام معنا.
She replied pretty fast.
أجابت بسرعة كبيرة.
I'm eating vegetarian tonight.
سأتناول طعاماً نباتياً الليلة.
I won't be coming.
لن آتي.
Did you say something
هل قلت شيئاً؟
to Jiang Mu?
إلى جيانغ مو؟
She hasn't been coming over lately.
لم تعد تأتي إلينا مؤخراً.
I did.
فعلتُ.
Can you cook faster?
هل يمكنك الطبخ بشكل أسرع؟
Can you drive faster?
هل يمكنك القيادة بشكل أسرع؟
I'd like to drive faster.
أرغب في القيادة بسرعة أكبر.
The rotors on your car are completely worn out.
أقراص الفرامل في سيارتك بالية تماماً.
If I drive any faster, it will fall apart.
إذا قدت بسرعة أكبر، فسوف ينهار.
Just step on it.
ما عليك سوى الضغط عليها.
If you can wreck it, I'll be impressed.
إذا استطعت تدميره، فسأكون منبهراً.
Turn off the AC while driving.
أطفئ مكيف الهواء أثناء القيادة.
The food will taste different if it gets cold.
سيختلف طعم الطعام إذا برد.
People will say my cooking is bad.
سيقول الناس إن طبخي سيء.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Come back quickly.
عد سريعاً.
We still have 7 or 8 more orders to deliver.
لا يزال لدينا 7 أو 8 طلبات أخرى لتسليمها.
When will my food arrive? I'm starving.
متى سيصل طعامي؟ أنا أتضور جوعاً.
Ten minutes.
عشر دقائق.
Why is it taking so long?
لماذا يستغرق الأمر كل هذا الوقت؟
Your restaurant's delivery is too slow.
خدمة توصيل مطعمكم بطيئة للغاية.
I'm going to file a complaint.
سأقدم شكوى.
If you had come before 7,
لو كنت قد أتيت قبل الساعة السابعة،
she wouldn't have thrown water on you.
لم تكن لتسكب عليك الماء.
♪ See the light that pulls me far ♪
♪ انظر إلى النور الذي يجذبني بعيدًا ♪
♪ Chase the whispers where you are ♪
♪ اتبع الهمسات أينما كنت ♪
♪ Through the echoing that still string ♪
♪ عبر صدى ذلك الوتر الساكن ♪
♪ Every step that takes me away ♪
♪ كل خطوة تأخذني بعيدًا ♪
So it was just a dream.
إذن كان مجرد حلم.
♪ Away from the noise and endless fights ♪
♪ بعيدًا عن الضوضاء والمشاجرات التي لا تنتهي ♪
This is too much.
هذا كثير جداً.
Can't you control yourself
ألا تستطيع السيطرة على نفسك؟
and stop thinking about all this nonsense?
وأتوقف عن التفكير في كل هذا الهراء؟
♪  Through the quite of your light ♪
♪ عبر سكون نورك ♪
But what does he
لكن ماذا يفعل؟
really think of me?
هل تفكر بي حقاً؟
♪ I'll break the chains of life's gray ♪
♪ سأكسر قيود الحياة الرمادية ♪
♪ Take me far and take me away ♪
♪ خذني بعيدًا وخذني بعيدًا ♪
Am I overthinking this?
هل أبالغ في التفكير في هذا الأمر؟
Or do you just...
أم أنك فقط...
want something to happen...
أريد أن يحدث شيء ما...
♪ Wind is howling and calling me ♪
♪ الريح تعوي وتناديني ♪
♪ Through the forest to the sea ♪
♪ عبر الغابة إلى البحر ♪
between us?
بيننا؟
♪ Shadows dances, the sky turns grey ♪
♪ ترقص الظلال، وتتحول السماء إلى اللون الرمادي ♪
♪ But your voice still leads my ♪
♪ لكن صوتك لا يزال يقودني ♪
♪ Away from the noise and endless fights ♪
♪ بعيدًا عن الضوضاء والمشاجرات التي لا تنتهي ♪
♪  Through the quite of your light ♪
♪ عبر سكون نورك ♪
♪ I'll break the chains of life's gray ♪
♪ سأكسر قيود الحياة الرمادية ♪
So annoying.
مزعج للغاية.
♪ Take me far and take me away ♪
♪ خذني بعيدًا وخذني بعيدًا ♪
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
that he was serious...
أنه كان جاداً...
about what he said?
بخصوص ما قاله؟
♪ The stars are whispering secrets true ♪
♪ النجوم تهمس بأسرار حقيقية ♪
♪ A pass unknown yet I'll pursue ♪
♪ سأسعى وراء ممر لم يُعرف بعد ♪
♪ With every breath I hear you say ♪
♪ مع كل نفس أسمعك تقول ♪
♪ You're waiting for me come away ♪
♪ أنت تنتظرني لأرحل ♪
It's already dawn.
لقد بزغ الفجر بالفعل.
♪ Away from the noise and endless fights ♪
♪ بعيدًا عن الضوضاء والمشاجرات التي لا تنتهي ♪
Jiang Mu,
جيانغ مو,
pull yourself together.
استجمع قواك.
Otherwise, how are you going to face him in the future?
وإلا، كيف ستواجهه في المستقبل؟
♪  Through the quite of your light ♪
♪ عبر سكون نورك ♪